McConnell, John W., Papers /3052
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Pettibone Corp, Rome NY vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local Lodge 1512, District Lodge 157, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  7/26/1977
- Philon Co. Inc., R.E. of E. Longmeadow, MA vs. Local 226, International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  7/24/1971
- Pinkham Lumber Company, a Division of Great Northern Paper Co vs. United Paper workers International Union, Local 1310, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  2/7/1975
- Pinkham Lumber Company, a Division of Great Northern Paper Co vs. United Paper workers International Union, Local 1310, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  12/14/1976
- Pine Valley Central School District, South Dayton, NY vs. Pine Valley Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  11/20/1974
- Poughkeepsie, NY, City of vs. Poughkeepsie Patrolmens Benevolent Association, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  12/23/1975
- Pratt, Read and Company, Ivoryton, Connecticut vs. United Furniture Workers of America, Local 105, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  8/1/1975
- Providence Grav?, Inc. vs. Providence Newspaper Web Pressmens Union, Local 12, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  5/1/1974
- Providence, R.I. School Committee vs. Providence Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, Local 958, McConnell as chairman, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  2/6/75, 4 volumes of transcripts re the matter of arbitration between Publishers' Association of NY City for member Long Island Daily Press and NY Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union No 2 dated 3/23/60, 3/24/60, 4/13/60, and 5/20/60
- Publishers Association of NYC for member Long Island Daily Press vs. NY Newspaper Printing Pressmens Union No. 2 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  no award in file folder, only McConnell's handwritten notes
- Publishers Association of NYC for member Long Island Daily Press vs. NY Newspaper Printing Pressmens Union No. 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Publishers Association of NYC for member Long Island Daily Press vs. NY Newspaper Printing Pressmens Union No. 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  no award in folder file
- Red Jacket Central School District vs. Red Jacket Faculty Association, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  6/25/1975
- Reed National Corporation., Westfield, Massachusetts vs. United Automobiles International Union, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers, Local 430, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  12/9/1977
- Regional Transit Service, Rochester, NY vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 282, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  10/25/1974
- Republic Foil, Inc, Danbury, Connecticut vs. International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers, Local 1251, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  5/15/1970
- Republic Foil Corp, Rolling Mill Division, Daraburry Connecticut, vs. International Union of United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1251, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  4/6/1976
- Revue Racing Association vs. Building Service Employees, Local 410 AFL-CIO (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Rhode Island Board of Regents vs. Rhode Island Dept. of Education, Professional Employees Union, Local 1012, American Federation of Teachers, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Rhode Island Board of Regents, R.I. School for the Deaf and Davies Vocational Technical High School vs. Deaf/Davies Teachers Association, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Richmond Rece Dye Works, Inc. vs. Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  11/19/1952
- Rily and Sons, Inc. W.H vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Work house men and Helpers, Local 653, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  10/5/1974
- Ripley Central School District vs. Ripley Education Association, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  10/17/1977
- Robertson Paper Box Company, Montville, Connecticut vs. District 50 of the United Mine Workers of America, Local 14977, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  9/23/1967
- Robertson Paper Box Company, Montville, Connecticut vs. District 50 of the United Mine Workers of America, Local 14977 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Robertson Paper Box Co., Montville, Connecticut vs. International Union Allied Technical Workers of America, District 50, Local 14977, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  1/26/1971
- Rockland, Maine Board of Directors, Maine School Administrative District ( MSAD) # 5 vs. The Teachers Association MSAD # 5, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  1/9/1973
- Rogers Corp, Rogers, Connecticut vs. United Paper Workers International Union, Oak Lodge, Rogers Local 46, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  11/19/1975
- Romulus Central School District Board of Education vs. Romulus Central School Facility Association, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  8/3/1973
- Ross and Roberts, Inc, Stratford, Connecticut, vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 837, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  3/28/1977
- Ross and Roberts, Inc, Stratford, Connecticut, vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Local 837, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  12/5/1977
- Royal Typewriter Co vs. Royal Industrial Union (Box 25, Folder 10)
  no award, case postponed and held in suspense
- Rush Henrietta Central School District vs. Rush Henrietta Education Association, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Saint Albans Billows Falls Free Academy vs. the BFA Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  8/30/1974
- Saint Albans, Vermont City of vs. AFSCME, Local 1343, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  6/7/1973
- Saint Lawrence County, NY vs. CSEA, St. Lawrence County Chapter, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Schroon Lake Central School vs. Schroon Lake C.S. Teachers Association, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  1/12/1979
- Scituate, Rhode Island School Committee vs. Scituate Teachers Association, McConnell as fact finder (Box 25, Folder 16)
  no award issued
- Scituate, Rhode Island School Committee vs. Scituate Teachers Association, McConnell as fact finder, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  1/23/1978
- Scott Graphics, Inc, Ternifax Division vs. General Mac Arthur Lodge # 1544, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  10/10/1971
- Scovill Manufacturing Co, Waterbury Division vs. Local 1604 of the International Union of United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Workers of America, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  1/31/1968
- Scovill Manufacturing Co, Waterbury Division vs. Local 1604 of the International Union of United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Workers of America, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  5/26/1969
- Scovill Manufacturing Co, Waterbury Division vs. Local 1604 of the International Union of United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Workers of America (Box 26, Folder 2)
  matter withdrawn from arbitration, no award
- Seacoast Education Association vs. School Board Supervisory Union21, McConnell as mediator (Box 26, Folder 3)
  no arbitration award
- Seymour, Connecticut, Board of Education vs. Seymour Education Association, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  10/4/1977
- Seneca, County of, NY vs. Seneca County Employees Association, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  5/28/1974
- Sheffield Tube Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local Lodge 1279, District 104, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  11/11/1972
- Silver Lake Regional School Committee, Kingston, MA, vs. Silver Lake Regional Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  12/3/1976
- Simkins Industries, New Haven, Connecticut vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 457, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  9/16/1974
- Simkins Industries, New Haven, Connecticut vs. United Paperworkers International Union, Local 457, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  6/28/1972
- Simplex Wire and Cable Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2208 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Simplex Wine and Cable Co vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2261 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Slater Paper Box Co, Fall River, MA vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Papermill Workers, Local 176 AFLCIO, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  4/15/1972
- Smithfield School Committee, Smithfield, RI vs. the NEA- Smithfield, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  4/23/1979
- South Colonie Central School District, Albany, NY vs. the South Colonie Teachers Association, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  10/6/1977
- Southworth Machine Co vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 895, AFL-CIO, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  7/12/1971
- Spaulding Moss, Incorporated, Westwood, MA vs. graphic Arts International Union, Local 300, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  9/21/1978
- Spaulding Division, Questor Corporation, Chicopee, MA vs. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, Local Lodge 1851, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  1/24/1979
- Special Metal Corp, New Hartford, NY vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 2310, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  5/11/1974
- Speidel, A Textron Company vs. Jewelry, Tool-workers and Die Cutter, IMA District 64, Lodge 129, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  6/28/1978
- Spencerport Central School District vs. Spencerport Teachers Association, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Spencerport Central School District vs. Spencerport Teachers Association, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  11/27/1973
- Springfield Cast products, Inc., Directly Affiliated Labor Union # 24 850 Retirement Income Plan Board of Administration (Co. Members) vs. Springfield Cast Products, Inc., DALU # 24 850, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  Retirement Income Plan, Board of Administration. (Union Members) Springfield, MA, first award 1/9/75, final award 2/21/75
- Springfield, MA, City of vs. Local 15347 of the Allied Technical Workers, fact-finding, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Springfield School Committee, Springfield, MA vs. Springfield Federation of Teachers, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  1/10/1977
- Springfield School Committee, Springfield, MA vs. Springfield Federation of Teachers, Local 484, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Springfield, VT, School Board vs. Springfield Teachers Association, McConnell as mediators (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Stafford, Connecticut Board of Education vs. Stafford Federation Association, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  7/28/1977
- State Department, Washington, D.C. vs. James C. Marshall, grievant before the Foreign Service Grievance Board, Mc Connell as chair person (Box 27, Folder 8)
  no date on rough draft of Board decision
- State Department, Washington, D.C. vs. W S. Krason, grievant before the FSGB, Mc Connell as chair (Box 27, Folder 9)
  no date on Board order
- State Department, Washington, D.C. vs. Michael P. Strutzel, grievant before the F.S.G.B, McConnell as chair (Box 27, Folder 10)
  no date on board order
- State Department, Washington, D.C. vs. Richmond Allen, grievant before F.S.G.B, McConnell as chair (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Stratford Board of Education, Stratford, CT vs. Stratford Education Association, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  10/5/1976
- Strathmore Paper Co, West Springfield, MA vs. United Paper workers and Paper workers, Local 197, AFL-CIO, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  2/28/1971
- Strathmore Paper Co, Turners Falls, MA vs. United Paper Workers and Paper workers, Local 171, AFL-CIO, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  10/25/1971
- Susquehanna Valley Central School District Board of Education vs. Susquehanna Valley Teachers Association, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  12/13/1974
- Swansea School Committee vs. Swansea Teachers Association, McConnell as mediatory/ fact-finder, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  11/11/1971
- Sweet Home Central School District, Amherst, NY vs. Sweet Home Education Association, NY State United Teachers (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Sweet Home Central School District, Amherst, NY vs. Sweet Home Education Association, NY State United Teachers, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  6/2/1976
- Swift and Co vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers Workmen of America (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Four cases: Symington Wayne Corporation (Symington Division) Depew, NY vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 1630, grievant: Alfred Golden, Atlas Tilford, Conrad Booker and Chpola Castings, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  6/4/1962
- Syracuse Rendering Co vs. Truck Drivers and Helpers, Local Union 317 of the International Brotherhood of Teamster of America, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  1/27/1962
- TRW-Holyoke Wire and Cable Co. vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 259, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  9/14/1976
- TRW Corp Holyoke Wire and Cable Co. vs. United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, Local 264, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  6/12/1978
- Taynton Co, Inc, H.W. vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 529, Elmira, NY (Box 28, Folder 13)
  no award found in File Folder
- Telescope Furniture Co. Inc, Granville, NY vs. United Furniture Workers of America, Local 36, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  8/20/1963
- Textron, Inc, Gorham Company, Providence, RI vs. Metals and Graft Workers Union, Local 16031, Allied and Technical Workers, 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  award 6/12/72, McConnell's response to a request for clarification, 4/18/74
- Transcript of Arbitration Hearing, Case 1130-0197-71, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  July 2, 1971
- Transcript of Arbitration Hearing, Case 1130-0197-71, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  Vol. 1, March 2, 1972
- Transcript of Arbitration Hearing, Case 1130-0197-71, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  Vol. 2, March 3, 1972
- Transcript of Arbitration Hearing, Case 1130-0197-71, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  Vol. 3, March 3, 1972
- Tompkins County, NY vs. CSEA, Tompkins County Chapter, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Tompkins County Board of Representatives, NY vs. CSEA, Tompkins County Chapter (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Torin Corporation, Avi Moving Division, Torrington CT vs. International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 507, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  8/17/1971
- Torrington Company (Excelsior Plant) vs. Metal Products Workers Union, Local 1645 of the UAW, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  6/27/1978
- Torrington Co, ( Broad Street Plant), Torrington, Connecticut vs. Metal Workers Union Local 1645 of the UAW, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  3/27/1978
- Torrington Co, (without Broad Street Plant), Torrington, Connecticut vs. Metal Workers Union Local 1645 of the UAW, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  6/21/1979
- Townsend Co, Tubular Rivet and Stud Division, a subsidiary of Textron vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Granite Lodge # 1451, AFL-CIO, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  2/19/1971
- Two Cases; Trailways of New England, Continental Trailways, Boston, MA vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 1318, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  4/11/77 on one award, no date on second award, McConnell as chairperson
- Two Cases; Trailways of New England, Continental Trailways, Boston, MA vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, Division 1318, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  7/20/75, McConnell as chair
- Transport of New Jersey vs. the Amalgamated Transit Union of Transport of N.J, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  12/14/1974
- Troy, NY, City of vs. City of Troy Unit of Rensselaer County Chapter of CSEA (Box 29, Folder 11)
  no awards contained in FF
- Trumbull, CT, town of vs. Trumbull Police Union Local 1745 of the CT Council of Police Unions (Box 29, Folder 12)
  no award found in FF
- U.S.M. Corp Fastener Division, Shelton, CT vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6150, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  7/11/1975
- Uniloy- Springfield, a division of Hoover Ball and Bearing Co, Springfield, MA vs. Directly Affiliated Labor Union 24850, AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Union Springs Central School vs. Union Springs Teachers Association, McConnell as mediatory (Box 30, Folder 1)
- United States Envelope Co., Worcester, MA vs. United Paper workers and Paper workers, AFL-CIO, Local 876 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  6/27/1970
- U.S. Postal Service, Buffalo, NY vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, AFL-CIO (Box 30, Folder 3)
  6/20/1977
- U.S.P.S., Oswego, NY vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 190 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  6/14/1978
- 2 cases: USPS, Rochester, NY vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 210 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  1/13/78 Janowski, 1/14/78 Caulker
- 2 cases: USPS, Rochester NY vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 210, Lyons and Hoover (Box 30, Folder 6)
  1/22/1979
- USPS, Rochester NY, vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 210 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Waverly (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Webster School Committee and Webster Teachers Assoc. (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Weedsport CSD - TA (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Weedsport CSD - TA [cont.] (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Weedsport CSD - TA [cont.] (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Wells Fargo Alarm - IBEW (Box 31, Folder 6)
- West Seneca, Central School (Box 31, Folder 7)
- U.P.P. Local 372 and Weyerhaeuser Company (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Whitesboro Teachers Assoc. Bd. Of Education - Whitesboro Central School (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Whitesboro CDS - WTA (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Local 276 I.U.E. and Wilbraham Manufacturing Company (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Williamsville School District (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Wilmington, Vermont (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Windham Northeast (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Windsor Central School (Box 31.1, Folder 1)
- Woburn Teachers Association (Box 31.1, Folder 2)
- National Marine Engineers Beneficial Assoc. (Box 31.1, Folder 3)
- Woonsocket R.I. - Fire Fighters (Box 31.1, Folder 4)
- Woonsocket - Locals 1139, 1402, 74, Int. Assoc. Firefighters (Box 31.1, Folder 5)
- Woonsocket School - Teacher G. (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Worcester MA, City of, vs. IAFF #1009: Correspondence, FF Report (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Worcester, MA, City of vs. IAFF #1009: Union Exhibits (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Worcester, MA, City of vs. IAFF #1009: Union Exhibits [cont.] (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Worcester, MA, City of vs. IAFF #1009: Union Exhibits (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Worcester, MA, City of vs. IAFF #1009: Union Exhibits [cont.] (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Worcester, MA, City of vs. IAFF #1009: City Exhibits (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Worcester, MA, City of vs. IAFF #1009: City Exhibits [cont.] (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Worcester, MA, City of vs. IAFF #1009: Union Exhibits (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Worcester, MA, City of vs. IAFF #1009: Union Exhibits [cont.] (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Worcester, MA, City of vs. IAFF #1009: City Exhibits (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Worcester, MA, City of vs. IAFF #1009: City Exhibits [cont.] (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Worcester, MA, City of vs. IAFF #1009: Briefs (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Worcester, MA, City of vs. IAFF #1009: Briefs [cont.] (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Worthington Pump Cases (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Arbitration Cases (Box 33, Folder 4)
- American Arbitration Association (Box 33, Folder 5)
- American Arbitration Assoc. (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Massachusetts Teacher Assoc. (Box 33, Folder 7)
- F.S. Payne - IAM (Box 33, Folder 8)
- American Economic Association Meeting, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- American Labor Educ. Service (Box 34, Folder 2)
- American Labor Educ. Service [cont.] (Box 34, Folder 3)
- John B. Andrews Memorial Symp. On Labor Leg. And Social Security, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Annual Conference on the Teaching of Labor Economics, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Annual Meeting of the Conf. Bd., NCIB, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Annual meeting of the Conf. Bd., NICB, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Annual Wage Issues Seminar, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Arbitration Conference - Rochester, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Arbitration Conference - Oct. 21-22, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Collective Bargaining (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Conference on Education and Social Security, Washington, D.C., 1949 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Conference on Medical and Community Aspects of Rehabilitation in Industry, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Conference on Wage and Salary Stabilization, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Cornell, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Cornell, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Cornell, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Cornell, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Cornell, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Cornell, 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Cornell [cont.], 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Chapter Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Questionnaire - Survey - Drafts - Revisions (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Personnel (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Pensions Committee (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Pension Study - Memos, Comments (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Cornell Social Science Research Ctr. (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Cornell Unemployment Ins. (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Current Material - 1958 Program (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Educators' Conference, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Empire State Chamber of Commerce, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Extension Conferences with Unions (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Faculty Legislation - ILR (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Faculty Legislation - University (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Federal Advisory Council on Employment Security (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Federation Employment & Guidance Service (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Governor's Conf. on Problems of the Aging (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Health, Welfare and Pension Plans Seminar, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- I (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Industrial Relations Research Assoc. (Box 35, Folder 21)
- General Organization of the ILR School (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Minutes of ILR Faculty Meetings (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Research Program - ILR (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Correspondence - India (Box 35, Folder 25)
- Iszard Company (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Iszard Company [cont.] (Box 35, Folder 27)
- J (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Joint Legislative Committee on Unempl. Ins. 2-day Meeting Ithaca - Aug. - 1957 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- K (Box 36, Folder 3)
- L (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Labor Market Research Conference, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Local and Long-Distance Movers (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Long Range Planning (Box 36, Folder 7)
- M (Box 36, Folder 8)
- McC (Box 36, Folder 9)
- McConnell's notes on housing (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Memorandums (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Michigan Unemployment Ins. System (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Morrison-Outline of Studies (Box 36, Folder 13)
- N (Box 36, Folder 14)
- National Conf. on Retirement of Older Workers', 1952 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- N.Y.S. Bills (Box 36, Folder 16)
- NYS Joint Legislative Comm. On Unempl. Ins., 1957 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- NYS Joint Legislative Comm. On Unempl. Ins. [cont.], 1957 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- NY Unempl. Ins. (Box 36, Folder 19)
- O (Box 36, Folder 20)
- P (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Personal (Box 36, Folder 22)
- R (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Resume - John W. McConnell (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Regional Wage Stabilization Manual (War Labor Board) (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Materials re: Retirement (Box 37, Folder 4)
- S (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Fred Slavik (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Correspondence. Proposed Social Security Center (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Social Welfare Conference (Box 37, Folder 8)
- State University of New York (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Stockholm Materials (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Survey of Retired Employment (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Survey of Retired Employees A-C (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Survey of Retired Employees D-H (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Survey of Retired Employees I-P (Box 37, Folder 14)
- T (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Travel Requests & Travel Vouchers (Box 37, Folder 16)
- U (Box 37, Folder 17)
- UNH (Box 37, Folder 18)
- SUNY Education Dept. (Box 37, Folder 19)
- V (Box 37, Folder 20)
- W (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Wage Stabilization Board (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Wage Stabilization Board [cont.] (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Wage Stabilization Board (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Wage Stabilization Board [cont.] (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Wage Stabilization Board (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Wage Stabilization Board [cont.] (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Wage Stabilization Board, Region 2, Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Wage Stabilization Board Documents (Box 38, Folder 9)
- XYZ (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Unemployment Ins. Fund (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Unemployment Ins. Fund [cont.] (Box 39, Folder 2)
- NYS Dept. of Labor (Box 39, Folder 3)
- NYS Dept. of Labor [cont.] (Box 39, Folder 4)